[{"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388171", "answers": [{"answer": "The more the merrier", "id": "4Ythj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The more and the merrier", "id": "6ZKbC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The more and merrier", "id": "XTMcQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The more and more merrier", "id": "n7XyJ", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.885Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388171", "question": "Of course you can come to the party…………….", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.090Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388173", "answers": [{"answer": "Less fat/ more exercise", "id": "4TvJs", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The less fat / the more exercise", "id": "Caqd6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Less and less fat/ the more exercise", "id": "0XfGz", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Fatter/more exercise", "id": "faWsd", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.898Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388173", "question": "People should eat ………………….. and do ………………. to reduce the risk of heart attack", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.131Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388175", "answers": [{"answer": "more or less", "id": "9KqPW", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more than", "id": "QwnNH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more and more", "id": "6DwJx", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "less than", "id": "QUMpR", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.902Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388175", "question": "There are ………………….. diseases being treated by laser beams", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.142Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388177", "answers": [{"answer": "than", "id": "4aqIV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more than", "id": "Z51oX", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "better", "id": "f8PZ8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "better than", "id": "SYsNs", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.909Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388177", "question": "I would rather be a teacher ………………. a doctor", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.149Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388179", "answers": [{"answer": "the harder/ the better", "id": "3ov6A", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more/ the much", "id": "ca71W", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the hardest/ the best", "id": "ZDU9F", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the more hard/ the better", "id": "pKdL5", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.914Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388179", "question": "…………………… you study for these exams…………………. you will do", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.156Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c1694738817b", "answers": [{"answer": "the more difficult", "id": "Bm3vq", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "difficult more and more", "id": "vjFLf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more difficult than", "id": "d3WSf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more and more difficult", "id": "AryQU", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.918Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c1694738817b", "question": "It gets_____to understand what the professor has explained", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.164Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c1694738817d", "answers": [{"answer": "are more", "id": "kK59f", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "are little", "id": "L0IIb", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "are much", "id": "lkxuy", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "are very", "id": "7JPaq", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.924Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c1694738817d", "question": "The rooms in the front ............noisier those than the back", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.172Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c1694738817f", "answers": [{"answer": "as many money as", "id": "wasVu", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "as much money as", "id": "bi4pI", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "as much money than", "id": "EwV7l", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "as more money than", "id": "mUtvl", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.929Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c1694738817f", "question": "Mr Lam cannot earn ……………….. his wife", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.179Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388181", "answers": [{"answer": "is the nicest", "id": "KGuwf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is nicer than", "id": "du3dH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is nice", "id": "q6ZlV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "is the nicer", "id": "i4if8", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.935Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388181", "question": "Of the two sisters, Mary……………………….", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.186Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388183", "answers": [{"answer": "as intelligent as", "id": "vpUZl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "so more intelligent than", "id": "OVQ9s", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "few more intelligent than", "id": "QubQS", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "a lot more intelligent than", "id": "LUvq9", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.939Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388183", "question": "She is………………………….her colleagues", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.193Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388185", "answers": [{"answer": "less difficult", "id": "ysTJj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "more and more difficult", "id": "jtnCW", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "least difficult", "id": "v9U8R", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "less and less difficult", "id": "VtsYk", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.944Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388185", "question": "Try to do this test. It is …………………… than the others", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.199Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388187", "answers": [{"answer": "the higher its", "id": "Wb4yf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "its higher", "id": "PTqiY", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "higher than its", "id": "HHui6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "higher of its", "id": "PwoUI", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.948Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388187", "question": "The larger the drop of water, ………….. freezing temperature", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.207Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388189", "answers": [{"answer": "As much as people", "id": "iT8lU", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "More people", "id": "mcOL1", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "As many as people", "id": "8M2zq", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "People more", "id": "hwL5X", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.952Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388189", "question": "……………………… live in HCM City than in the whole of the rest of the country", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.213Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c1694738818b", "answers": [{"answer": "The more he works, the happier he feels", "id": "PEjxT", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The less he works, the happier he feels", "id": "ZcVrC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "His work makes him feel happy", "id": "eaunx", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "He feels happier and happier with his work", "id": "p6Rgx", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.956Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c1694738818b", "question": "He only feels happy whenever he does not have much work to do", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.221Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c1694738818d", "answers": [{"answer": "Tom plays well but others plays better", "id": "VK7av", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Tom as well as other players of the team plays very well", "id": "Q9sm9", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Everyone in the team, but Tom plays well", "id": "1Up7M", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Tom is the best player of the team", "id": "ux8ha", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.959Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c1694738818d", "question": "No one in the team plays better than Tom", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.227Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c1694738818f", "answers": [{"answer": "I learn more and more and remember more and more", "id": "NxcVQ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The more I learn, the less I remember", "id": "tGd3z", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "The more t learn, the more I remember", "id": "tYdu7", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "I remember not only what I have learnt", "id": "WjXlS", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.963Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c1694738818f", "question": "I learn a lot but I cannot remember anything", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.233Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388191", "answers": [{"answer": "Jane plays football very well", "id": "yir5r", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Jane plays football better than Kate", "id": "MV4Bc", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Jane plays football as well as Kate", "id": "NBa8q", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Jane plays football weller than Kate", "id": "Hdzde", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.966Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388191", "question": "Kate doesn’t play football as well as Jane", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.239Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388193", "answers": [{"answer": "I’m tall and my brother is short", "id": "DBcVj", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "I’m shorter than my brother", "id": "9Jfwl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "My brother is shorter than I does", "id": "aYSkh", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "My brother isn’t as tall as me", "id": "n7Hlr", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.971Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388193", "question": "I’m taller than my brother", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.246Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388195", "answers": [{"answer": "Older", "id": "dYrkP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "elder", "id": "9z23X", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the older", "id": "1mQ9e", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "both A and B", "id": "GAJxi", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.975Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388195", "question": "My …………….. sister is very good at English and Maths", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.253Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "5984f46f0238c16947388197", "answers": [{"answer": "the largest", "id": "rWKjw", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "the larger", "id": "3YKeN", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "one of  most large", "id": "Ey3zn", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "6lavp", "text": "One of  larger", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "wgWNT", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-04T22:25:51.979Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "5984f46f0238c16947388197", "question": "The HCM City is…………………… city in VietNam", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-05T01:05:56.260Z"}]